[{"answer": " Hey, Charlie.  How was the first day of class", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " It was OK.  I got lost this morning trying to find my first one.  I felt like such ", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hey, Charlie.  How was the first day of class", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Me too.  I cant believe how many we have to buy.  I need a book and a cours", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 17, "question": " It was OK.  I got lost this morning trying to find my first one.  I felt like such ", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Me too", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Me too.  I cant believe how many we have to buy.  I need a book and a cours", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Have you bought any of them yet", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Me too", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Not yet.  I looked online at the university bookstore though and each book i", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Have you bought any of them yet", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Thats so expensive!  How do they expect poor students to be able to pay fo", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Not yet.  I looked online at the university bookstore though and each book i", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Who knows?  Thats pretty steep though.  Its going to cost us $300 a term a", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Thats so expensive!  How do they expect poor students to be able to pay fo", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Did your professors say the university bookstore is the only place to buy th", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Who knows?  Thats pretty steep though.  Its going to cost us $300 a term a", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " No, they didnt say anything about where to buy them", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Did your professors say the university bookstore is the only place to buy th", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Maybe there is a better place to buy the books than the university bookstore", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No, they didnt say anything about where to buy them", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " I think there probably is.  You know, I heard there are a few other bookstore", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Maybe there is a better place to buy the books than the university bookstore", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 48, "question": " I think there probably is.  You know, I heard there are a few other bookstore", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Yeah.  The university bookstore only sells new ones, but the other stores sel", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Used books?  Do you think thats a good idea?  Arent they all marked-up an", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yeah.  The university bookstore only sells new ones, but the other stores sel", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I heard that some have been highlighted or written in some", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Used books?  Do you think thats a good idea?  Arent they all marked-up an", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Why would we pay for a book thats been used though", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 65, "question": " I dont think so.  I heard that some have been highlighted or written in some", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Well, its the exact same textbook and they sell for half the price of a new one", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Why would we pay for a book thats been used though", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Oh. Well, that sounds like a deal.  I dont think Id mind a used book if its s", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Well, its the exact same textbook and they sell for half the price of a new one", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Me neither.  Maybe we can go together later to the used textbook store", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Oh. Well, that sounds like a deal.  I dont think Id mind a used book if its s", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " OK.  Hey.  What about our course packets?  Where do we get those", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Me neither.  Maybe we can go together later to the used textbook store", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " All my professors said that we had to get those at the University Copy Stor", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 73, "question": " OK.  Hey.  What about our course packets?  Where do we get those", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Oh, right.  I remember now that my profs said that too.  Can we get thos", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 77, "question": " All my professors said that we had to get those at the University Copy Stor", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I think those are ordered to be printed specifically by th", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Oh, right.  I remember now that my profs said that too.  Can we get thos", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Why do we have to buy those", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 85, "question": " I dont think so.  I think those are ordered to be printed specifically by th", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " My brother said theyre usually a collection of articles.  They make us bu", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Why do we have to buy those", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Did he say if the course packets were expensive", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 89, "question": " My brother said theyre usually a collection of articles.  They make us bu", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " I dont think theyre too bad.  Between $30 and $60", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Did he say if the course packets were expensive", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " At least its not $100", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I dont think theyre too bad.  Between $30 and $60", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 92, "question": " At least its not $100", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Well, do you want to go the Copy Store after the bookstore tonight", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Sure.  We might as well buy everything at once", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Well, do you want to go the Copy Store after the bookstore tonight", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " How about 7:00", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Sure.  We might as well buy everything at once", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Sounds good.  Ill pick you up then", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 95, "question": " How about 7:00", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Cool.  See you then", "docId": "06-08", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Sounds good.  Ill pick you up then", "qSentId": 95}]
